moviesdrop.com 2016-06-28

# Slashsquare Network - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy of Slashsquare covers all the blogs under our Network. Please read this statement carefully before using or proceeding to access Slashsquare Sites. 

You have should read and understood this privacy policy and indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms of Use in effect. 

### Information Collected

We own the content on our blog, so there is no way a third-party can get access to it. We collect information from our readers on various circumstances like Guest Blogging, Commentating, Contest rules, so on. **But we will NEVER reveal them to others.**

**Guest Blogging**

In order to submit a guest post registration is enabled, so some information about you is collected on our database. That includes your name, nickname, bio, email address and other social media handles. Your details are safe with us. Registered Guest Authors may get rare updates from Slashsquare regarding our Guest Blogging system. 

**Commenting**

Visitors/Readers can comment on our blog(s) using their Name, Email address and Website (optional). Name and Email address are mandatory. As of now (23.12.2011) we are not using third-party commenting service like Disqus or Facebook. We use the default WordPress comment system. 

**Email Subscription**

If you are subscribed to the blogs under our network, you will get updates related to it on your mail. Slashsquare may from time to time track user email usage in a continued effort to improve our services. We rarely use our mailing lists for Advertising, we make that as the last option for Advertising. If it is an Advertisement, it will clearly be marked as advertising. Kindly remember you always have the option to unsubscribe if you don’t want any disputes. 

**Log Files**

Slashsquare makes use of use of log files. Normally all the websites do this. Log files contain information like Internet Protocol addresses, type of browsers used, Internet Service Provider, date/time stamp, referring sites, and no. of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, user’s movement over the site, and demographic information. Those information will never be leaked under any circumstances.

**External Links**

Slashsquare (and it’s blogs) contains external links for your references and they are not affiliated with us in any manner unless mentioned. Those sites are not governed by this privacy policy and Slashsquare is not responsible. Kindly read their own Policy before involving. If you find any misleading links you can [report to us](http://slashsquare.org/contact/).

###  Advertisements 

Advertisements help our network to run smoothly and boost for other services. We display ads only related to our sites niche. 

**First Party Ad Serving**

The ads appearing on this website are delivered to you by Technorati Media, our web advertising vendor. They have partnered with several networks that run campaigns from GoogleADX. Slashsquare uses only the first-party data. They will be used for proprietary ad delivery, ad reporting, and contextual advertising. They won’t share them with third-party advertisers. 

“First-party data refers to the information that visitors provide because of the relationship they have with a website or blog. This refers to the information that is shared either implicitly or explicitly.”

Google Adsense normally uses the DART cookie to serve advertisement based on user’s interest and previous interaction.

**Third Party Advertisements**

The advertisements given to us by our sponsors and dealers may distribute cookies to users. Unfortunately we don’t have much control over them. These advertisers may be engaging in online behavioral advertising. 

### Network Security

Slashsquare Network is guarded by various sources and we can assure you about its security infrastructure. Like we protect our blogs we also take care of the personal information about you deeply. Under our security practices and policies, we have limited the access to sensitive files and information for other users. 

If you find any security issue regarding our blog(s), feel free to ping us at **webmaster@slashsquare.org**

### Acquisition or Merger

When Slashsquare Network encounters business transitions like acquisition or merger by another company, users’ personal information will be part of the assets transferred. Like always your details will be in safe hands. 

Even after the acquisition or merger, your contributions and works for the network will be still. 

### Legal Disclaimer

We preserve user privacy and we respect Law as well. Slashsquare may need to disclose personal information when required by law. As long as we own this Network, your association with us, is safe.
